http://www.acb.org.uk/whatweare/privacy

Scientific committee
Clinical Sciences Reviews Committee (CSRC)
Immunology group
What is Immunology?
Immunology Resources
Immunology Events
Where is Immunology?
Quick Links
You are here:
Home/ What we are/ Privacy
What we are
PresidentAnnual reportEquality, Diversity & InclusionJoin the ACB
Application FormsMembership categoriesProfessional benefits of membershipFeesTax reliefEuropean Register for Specialists in Laboratory MedicineChartered ScientistACB Extras - Additional benefits
Contact and offices
Tooley StreetRoom Hire
Structure
ConstitutionCommitteesCouncilExecutiveNational meetings committeeFederation of Clinical Scientsts committeeScientific committee
Clinical Sciences Reviews Committee (CSRC)
Author Information Pack
National audit group
Communications & publications committees
Publications committeeACB News committeeAnnals committeeLabtestsonline committee
Education, training & workforce committees
Education committeeRegional tutorsTrainees committee
Immunology professional committeeMicrobiology professional committeeRepresentatives on other bodiesRegions
North West Region
CommitteePast Officials
Northern Ireland Region
NewsCommitteeNorthern Ireland Pathology NetworkLaboratory IndexRegional Audit GroupMeeting Documents
2013 Spring Scientific Meeting2012 Spring Scientific Meeting2011 Spring Scientific Meeting
Federation of Clinical ScientistsPast Officials
Republic of Ireland Region
CommitteePast Officials
Scotland Region
CommitteeJohn King AwardPast Officials
Southern Region
NewsCommitteeCommittee Meeting MinutesRegional Awards & BursariesPast Officials
South West & Wessex Region
NewsletterScientific MeetingsFor TraineesTrainees' AwardCommittee Meeting MinutesCommitteeLaboratory IndexPast OfficialsAudit
Trent Northern & Yorkshire Region
CommitteeGeoffrey Walker AwardLaboratory IndexBursariesPast Officials
Wales Region
CommitteeWales Clinical Biochemistry Audit GroupPast Officials
West Midlands Region
Robert Gaddie Memorial FundCommitteeLaboratory IndexDocumentsPast Officials
Fellows, Emeritus and Honorary members
Emeritus membersFellows of the AssociationHonorary members
Archive of officials and committee members
Former ACB honorary officer directors on Council
Former ACB honorary officer directors on Council 1953-2007
Former ACB national member directors on councilFormer FCS officersFormer scientific committees officersFormer education committees officersFormer publication committees officersFormer trainees committee officers
Corporate partners
List of Corporate Members
HistoryPrivacy
Further Links
ACB News Annals Trade Union Support
ACB Privacy Policy Who we are The Association for Clinical Biochemistry and Laboratory Medicine (ACB) is a professional body dedicated to the practice and promotion of clinical science. The ACB is a Registered Company in England (no. 863235) limited by guarantee. What we collect The types of personal information we collect may include your title, first name, surname, gender, date of birth, your qualifications, home and work contact details (telephone, fax, street address, email address, credit card details or bank details), demographic data and your mailing address. We may also collect information relating to your employment, including where you are currently employed, your job title, registration details, salary band, areas of interest/expertise and your job function if this is relevant to your membership. In applications for some categories of membership we ask you to identify a referee and to provide contact information for them.
When purchasing a product, your credit card details are also collected, and are temporarily stored until we have processed your order. How we handle your personal information The ACB respects the privacy of its members, customers and website users, and aims to act consistently within applicable legislation. Generally, the ACB collects personal information directly from you or via our website forms or when you interact directly with us in other ways. For example, we collect personal information when you:
Deal with us in person, by telephone, letter, fax or email Fill out and submit a Membership Application form Submit any other information in connection with your application for membership or the purchase of products and services Register for a journal subscription Make an enquiry via a web form Apply for a bursary or grant Register to attend an event Respond to a membership survey
Why we collect information We collect personal data to administer our activities, products, services or grants and bursaries. Maintaining the accuracy of data Personal data can be corrected or updated by contacting the ACB by email  Payment and bank details Any information provided by you in connection with a Direct Debit payment or transaction regarding your credit or debit card numbers, expiry date and billing or delivery address will be used by us to process the transaction.
Credit card details are not stored on our servers, but are securely stored on the payment gateways – Secure Trading Limited employed by the ACB. Use and disclosure The ACB’s policy is not to disclose any personal information that we hold on you to any unrelated third party, except where you have given your express consent for us to do so or where required by law.
Arrangements are occasionally made with suppliers of goods and services (such as other scientific societies for their mailings to be sent to members). All material is carefully vetted and the mailing list is never released to third parties. The ACB may use your email address for the purpose of notifying you about products, services, events or activities of relevance to you. If you tell us that you do not wish us to use your personal information for a particular purpose, we will not do so. Personal information will be used only for the purpose stated at the point of collection (such as the processing of grant applications) and such information will be held for as long as necessary to fulfil the stated purpose. The ACB (or its committee members/representatives) may, from time to time, email you with additional information considered to be relevant to your professional/scientific interests, but only to those who have given their agreement to receiving such communications. Security Information that you supply to the ACB is held securely and strict security procedures are followed to prevent unauthorized access or use. Information to improve our site We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site, including IP address, duration of visit, language, country and device settings. This information is used to help us follow browsing preferences on our site so that we can regularly improve our website and enable more advanced features of our website. Cookies on our site A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie folder of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are.
Where relevant, this website uses cookies to store login session information during your login session. If you choose to remember your login, then the cookie will be retained on your computer after you log out. By logging in to the system you are - by necessity - accepting these cookies. Access to personal information and correction of information If the information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or outdated, please inform us so that we can correct it. If you no longer wish to receive information from us, then please let us know using the contact details below. You can seek access to the personal information we hold about you, by contacting us. You should include your name, address and telephone number. In general there will be no charge for this information, but The Association for Clinical Biochemistry and Laboratory Medicine reserves the right to charge a reasonable fee in response to an access request. How to contact us: The Association for Clinical Biochemistry and Laboratory Medicine
130-132 Tooley Street
LONDON
SE1 2TU
Tel: 020 7403 8001
Fax: 020 7403 8006
Email:
Updated 24 May 2018
© Copyright The Association for Clinical Biochemistry and Laboratory Medicine
ACB Store | ACB News | Annals | Site Map | Contact Us | LabtestsOnline | Privacy statement
The Association for Clinical Biochemistry
and Laboratory Medicine
130-132 Tooley Street LONDON SE1 2TU
Tel: 020 7403 8001 Fax: 020 7403 8006
